hey everyone Mr popid here I wanted to
do a breakdown of this product retinol
Advanced by yden um I received it about
two months ago I've been using it
nightly and I want to break down what
makes this different from a lot of the
others for starters it is expensive uh
you know this uh getting into this realm
of nighttime serums is common to have
$100 to $200 even more I've seen in some
of them and this has a lot if not
everything that you find in those other
ones so much so they had to separate it
there's some up here and there's some
down here and when you squirt it they
mix together and then they absorb and
get the job done um they would be
unstable if they were together so they
had they did have to separate them and
let's break down um you know what's in
here retin alahh is a cosmetic vitamin A
that's just close to a a prescription
strength retinoid that you can get
without getting a prescription it's
three times stronger than retinol r e t
i n o l uh and it's great at exfoliation
collagen stimulation um helping to kind
of smooth out the complexion and with
fine lines and wrinkles uh niacinamide
is also in here and that improves camide
production um it it's an antioxidant
that reduces stress uh you know
stressors from from uh oxidation and it
also helps with reducing redness and
irritation
melatonin is also something that
increases collagen syn synthesis it's an
antioxidant as well that's in here
vitamin C of scorb acid can be a little
unstable sometimes it's an antioxidant
that can improve collagen production but
they found a way to put all those
together and the key one that you hear
about a lot lately is bakuchiol and
bikol is a plant-based retinol
alternative and in clinical studies it
does a lot of the same things that
retinoids do without the irritation and
it is all natural it's from a plant uh I
believe it's in India overseas and it's
a very nice kind of soothing uh coupling
with having retin alide in there as well
uh so what these do collectively is
stimulate natural anti antioxidant
defenses and help restore vitality and
elasticity to give you more radiant kind
of glowing skin um and like you guys
know I don't I don't back anything until
I've tried it and and I got this months
ago and I have been trying it and you
can see my skin looks very smooth I've
actually gotten compliments and very
soft um the nice thing that I have found
about this even though there's retin
aldhy in it which is three times
stronger than retinols the other things
in it seem to kind of uh buffer the
irritation that you can get from a
topical retin alahh um or topical
vitamin A and and with anything though
even with puchel I've had some people
say they're sensitive to it uh start
slowly just do it two to three times a
week in the beginning 1.7 o should last
you about 2 and 1 half to 3 months at
$180 I know that's expensive it's not
for everybody but there are people out
there that spend way more than that on
five or six different creams and serums
and toners um this is a nice kind of
everything and one um to really get the
job done you don't see a big difference
in the first month it does take you know
going into that second month for you to
start to feel it because it is a slow
gradual Improvement so it's not going to
be in you know two weeks you're going to
see a big difference but sticking with
it you know I do recommend giving it a
try so I wanted to show you
here um I usually do two pumps you can
see right
here it mixes together you can see the
white and yellow there and I will then
rub that it's kind of a oil like serum
and you rub it on the face avoiding the
eyes it's a thin film goes on S
nice you can see there I get a little
bit up on the head too just cuz I don't
have hair there make sure to get the
nose nice pore tightening so that's how
it goes on um and you know it feels it's
nice and smooth it doesn't feel bad one
thing I like about this company with
dden is they really put the time and
money in with their microbiologists and
their scientists to make something that
feels great with their sunblock and with
this and what's important about that is
I have a lot of patients that are like I
didn't like the way that felt so I
didn't use it that is so common uh so
having something that feels great it
feels like it's working um you know
night after night when you start to feel
that smoothness it's usually a great
outcome um and you know just it's not
for everybody if you try it you don't
like it great and put it on in the
comments I I want to hear your feedback
um I like to try these things and see
what I think about it before I would
ever recommend it to you I get you know
five offers a day for products all the
time for the last year and a half since
I passed 500,000 subscribers um and
there's so many things I just you know I
really pick and choose before I would
introduce it to you so if you like it
there's a link uh and you can click it
in this video and then Isen favorites 15
is 15% off everything um on their on
their site is.com so I hope you enjoy it
thanks for popping by and uh any
questions put it in the comments section